Senior Software Engineer

Senior Software engineer with 6+ years of experience to love blockchain engineering very much. Jobs said, "Stay hungry, Stay foolish".

I love this phrase and am always eager to learn and accept new things. I like to challenge and focus on the blockchain.

ABOUT ME

Senior Software Engineer

I am a software engineer to love the blockchain very much.

It is so fun working with blockchain in my life. So I am focusing on blockchain development.

Before developing blockchain projects, I have done many full-stack web projects. MERN and MEAN stack are my main skills.

After that for 3 years, I have been focused on the blockchain, so I have done many blockchain projects.

According to the development, I have deep knowledge of this side. so I am flexible with new blockchain skills.

If you are looking for a blockchain & full-stack developer, feel free to contact me.

PERSONAL INFO

LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/paul-martin-a05534232

Email: paulmartin.pm1125@gmail.com Skype: live:.cid.8e6b51448484a913

Telegram: https://t.me/gru1125

Discord: Gru#9712

GitHub: https://github.com/FeloniousGru-Super

Phone: +1 904 330 5956

Website: https://paulmartin-1125.web.app/

SKILLS

❖ Blockchain

- Ethereum | Binance Smart Chain | Polygon | AVAX | Solana
- DAO | DeFi | NFT | Marketplace | P2E | Token
- Web3.js | Ether.js | Solana-Web3 | UseDapp | Moralis | Subgraph
- Smart Contract | Solidity | Remix | HardHat | Truffle
- Program | Rust | Anchor | Metaplex | Candy Machine
- IPFS | Arweave

Front End

- React.js | Vue | Angular | Next.js | Redux | Vuex
- HTML | CSS | Boostrap | Tailwind CSS | JavaScript | TypeScript
- Material UI | Ant Design
- Socket

Back End & Server

- Node.js | Express | Laravel | Django | Python | Ruby on Rails
- MySQL | MongoDB | PostgreSQL | Firebase
- Mongoose | Sequelize
- GraphQL | Apollo | Restful API
- Git | SVN | NgInx
- AWS | Lambda | CloudFront | EC2 | S3 | NgInx | PM2

Senior Software Engineer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Blockchain Engineer

Freelance 05/2021 - Present

- Built P2E NFT Game on BSC network <u>CryptoLegions</u>.
- Built P2E NFT Game on Harmony network WenLambo.
- Built DAO on BSC network similar to OlympusDAO <u>EverVault</u>.
- Built Defi with Staking feature on Polyon Network <u>HyperMatic</u>.
- Built <u>CasperPad</u> Site with token sale, vesting and staking feature. (My client has earned **700,000** USD within **5** hours.)
- Built game portal site with React. Ghospers.
- Implement token airdrop with Suni token in the smart contract with Solidity on BSC network for <u>SassyUnicorns</u>.
- Mint and Built Lunachow token & Lunachow NFT Marketplace.
- Built the FTE with React for New Eco-System will be called <u>Zeroloss</u>.
- Developed the system to show the status and log of transactions as real-time following users by using Chart and Material Theme.
- Environment: Blockchain, DApps, Ethereum, BSC, Solana, Solidity, Rust, Metaplex, Candy Machine, Hyperledger,
 Truffle, Ganache, HardHat, Remix, Web3.js, Wallet, React, Vue, Node.js, Laravel, Express, ES5, ES6, MySQL, MongoDB,
 Postman, Tailwind CSS

Blockchain Engineer

Catalant 02/2021 - 04/2021

- Built NFT minting site Procamelriders.
- Built the profile page of the betting site BitSport.
- Implemented complex UI components with React / Vue / TypeScript and SCSS, Tailwind CSS.
- **Environment:** Blockchain, DApps, Ethereum, BSC, Solana, Solidity, Rust, Hyperledger, Truffle, Remix, Web3.js, React, Vue, Node.js, ES6 Postman, Tailwind CSS

Blockchain Developer

Freelance 02/2019 - 12/2020

- Built NFT minting and NFT marketplace and integrate with OpenSea.
- Built the system to display the transaction logs as real-time in a chart and table using API.
- Worked on providing API endpoints with Node.js/Inversify, GraphQL and MongoDB.
- **Environment**: Blockchain, DApps, Ethereum, Solidity, Ganache, Remix, Web3.js, React, Next.js, Node.js, Python, ES6, MySQL, MongoDB, Postman, Tailwind CSS

Senior Front-end Developer

UpCounsel 03/2018 - 12/2018

- Led the front-end development of a multilingual digital rehabilitation platform.
- Used Angular 7 and NgRx to make the Reactive front end.
- Migrated admin merged an admin panel application into the platform with React.js.
- Built from scratch a product website with Vue, Angular and React.JS.
- Implemented the connecting the UI to the API and also optimized the website to make the user experience great.
- **Environment**: React, Angular, Vue, Node.js, Restful API, GraphQL, MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Postman, Material UI, ANTD

Senior Software Engineer

Full Stack Developer

PCM-logistics LLC 01/2017 - 01/2018

- Build the project for company Nitanta.
- This project involves several features employee management, discussing, communication tool, project management.
- Developed the discussing tool like Stackoverflow.
- Built communication tool like discord.
- Built the project management like Trello.
- Environment: Vue.js, Vuex, Vuetify, ES6, Laravel, MySQL, Socket, Pusher, Restful API, Postman

Senior Javascript Developer SOARZROCK NAGOYA 02/2016 - 12/2016

- Built the communication tool (Video, Voice, Chatting).
- Implemented the video streaming and socket.
- Built Pony site.
- Environment: React, Socket, Streaming, MongoDB, Node, Postman, Ruby on Rails

JS Core Developer

Google 05/2015 - 11/2015

PHP Developer

UACJ Nagoya Sight 03/2014 - 11/2014

- Built the system to manage employees by using Laravel.
- Served the project with the apache server.
- Environment: PHP, Laravel, Html, CSS, JavaScript, Apache, Xampp

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science *Meijo University*

CERTIFICATION (https://triplebyte.com/tb/paul-martin-ieonx4h/certificate)



Senior Software Engineer

PROJECTS

- Cryptolegions

https://play.cryptolegions.app - Private Repo from Organization

Cutting edge Play-To-Earn NFT game on the BSC network, with a genius system for a sustainable game economy. This is the first Play-To-Earn NFT Game with a Revolutionary Omni-Balanced Oracle Sustainability System. There are NFT minting and NFT marketplace functions in this project.

And special tax ecosystem.

React | Redux | Web3 | TypeScript | Material UI | Node.js | MySQL Smart Contract with Solidity on BSC | HardHat AWS | Firebase | Heroku | Discord Bot Integration

- WenLambo

https://wenlambo.one/

NFT P2E Game on Harmony Network - https://github.com/FeloniousGru-Super/WenLamboApp-P2E-NFT-Game There are NFT minting and NFT marketplace functions in this project. And there will be a race mission function, this will be the Metaverse.

React | Redux | Web3 | Tailwind CSS | Node.js | MongoDB | Resful API Smart Contract with Solidity on Harmony | HardHat

- Suni Token Airdrop

https://sassyunicorns.io/

Base token (Suni) airdrop on BSC - https://github.com/FeloniousGru-Super/Suni-Token-Airdrop-SassiUnicorn Built Smart Contract for token airdrop, once users have NFT on this site.

Smart Contract with Solidity on BSC | Remix

- ProcamelRiders

https://procamelriders.com/

This is a simple NFT minting site - https://github.com/FeloniousGru-Super/CamelRiders-NFT-minting.

Pro Camel Riders are 9,999 unique collectibles that display the beauty of the Arab world.

Each NFT is unique and programmatically generated using 100+ hand drawn assets.

It is working on the Ethereum network.

Built Front End and Smart Contract.

React | Node.js | Web3 Smart Contract with Solidity on Ethereum | Remix

- HyperMatic

https://www.hypermatic.finance/

Defi for Staking on Polygon network.

Users can withdraw the rewards related to the amount that they deposited.

It is working like Staking.

React | TypeScript | Web3 Smart Contract with Solidity on Polygon | HardHat

Senior Software Engineer

- CasperPad

https://casper-pad.io/

Staking Site, Token Sale with vesting and whitelist feature on BSC - https://github.com/FeloniousGru-Super/CasperPad In the first version, I implemented the presale with whitelist and vesting functions.

Base token is **\$CSPD**.

So client has earned 700,000 USD within 5 hours.

After that in the next version, built several kinds of public sale, and add Staking function.

https://sale.casper-pad.io/ - Public Sale

https://staking.casper-pad.io/ - Staking

In the staking site, users can stake \$CSPD, and harvest rewards.

And can buy \$CSPD...

React | Tailwind CSS | Node.js | UseDapp Smart Contract with Solidity on BSC | HardHat | Remix

- EverVault DAO

https://everdao-e90a4.web.app

This is similar to Olympus DAO on BSC. - https://github.com/FeloniousGru-Super/DAO-EverVault This used Pancakeswap.

Base token is \$EVE.

Developed the front end and Smart Contract

..

React | Tailwind CSS | Node.js | UseDapp Smart Contract with Solidity on BSC | HardHat | Remix

••••